Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- I, 299909
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Convention, 1970-1973; 300246 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Convention, 1976; 300247 (Box 44)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Convention, 1977; 300248 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Convention, 1978; 300249 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications, circa 1970s; 324456 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications, 1970-1975; 300250 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications, 1976-1977; 300251 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications, 1980-1981; 300252 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications I, undated; 300253 (Box 45)
  - International Socialists (U.S.): Pamphlets and Publications II, undated; 300254 (Box 45)
  - International Society for Labor Law and Social Legislation, undated; 300255 (Box 45)
  - International Solidarity Committee, 1936-1949; 300256 (Box 45)
  - International Solidarity Fund (Paris, France), circa 1938; 300257 (Box 45)
  - International Solidarity Movement, 2002-; 300258 (Box 45)
  - International Song Publishers, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 005, Folder 13)
  - International Student Conference (Nigeria), 1957; 300259 (Box 45)
  - International Student - Faculty Strike Day, 1968; 373679 (Box 45)
  - International Student Relief (Prague), 1950; 300260 (Box 45)
  - International Student Service, 1942-1948; 300261 (Box 45)
  - International Symposium on Anarchism (Portland, OR), 1980; 300262 (Box 45)
  - International Symposium on Imperialism Its Place in Social Science Today (Elsinore, Denmark), 1971; 300263 (Box 45)
  - International Trade Union Committee of Negro Workers, 1929, 1930, undated; 327841 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth I, 1956-1966; 300264 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth II, 1956-1966; 300265 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth III, 1956-1966; 300266 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Socialist Youth IV, 1956-1966; 300267 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students, 1949-1950; 300268 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students, 1950; 300269 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students, 1951-1960; 300270 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students, 1961-1970; 300271 (Box 45)
  - International Union of Students I, 1971-1979; 300272 (Box 46)
  - International Union of Students II, 1971-1979; 324491 (Box 46)
  - International Union of Students, 1980-; 300273 (Box 46)
  - International War Crimes Tribunal (Stockholm, Sweden; Roskilde, Denmark), 1967; 300274 (Box 46)
  - International Werewolf Conspiracy, undated; 324486 (Box 46)
  - International Women's Congress Against War and Fascism (Paris, France), 1934; 300275 (Box 46)
  - International Women's Day Committee (Great Britain), circa 1949; 300276 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Defense Conference (New York), 1914; 300277 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Defense League of San Francisco (California), 1918; 300278 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1930-1932; 300279 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1933-1939; 300280 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1940-1943; 300281 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1944; 300282 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1945; 300283 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1946-1948; 300284 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1950; 300285 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order, 1950-1951; 300286 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order I, undated; 300287 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order II, undated; 300288 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order III, undated; 300289 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order: Frederick Douglass Fraternal and Benevolent Society, undated; 300290 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order: Front Line Fighters Fund, 1942; 300291 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Order: Polonia Society, 1945; 300292 (Box 46)
  - International Workers Party (New York, NY), 1974-1975; 300293 (Box 46)
  - International Workingmen's Association, 1872-1933; 300294 (Box 46)
  - International Workingmen's Association, 1975-1981; 300295 (Box 46)
  - International Working Union of Socialistic Educational Organizations, 1923; 300296 (Box 46)
  - International Workmen's Association of America: German Section, 1885; 300297 (Box 46)
  - International Youth Alliance (New York, NY), undated; 300298 (Box 46)
  - Internationale Gewerkschaftsorganizationen Mahrens Koferenz, 1910; 300299 (Box 46)
  - International Ouvriere Socialiste, 1923; 300300 (Box 46)
  - Internationales Politisches Antiquariat, undated; 300301 (Box 46)
  - Internationalism (New York, NY), 1973-1979; 300302 (Box 46)
  - Internationalist Group (NY,NY), 1996-2001; 372988 (Box 46)
  - Internationalist Perspective (New York, NY), 1970-; 300303 (Box 46)
  - Internationalist Socialist League (Fourth International), undated; 324487 (Box 46)
  - Interracial Club (New York, NY), 1942; 300304 (Box 46)
  - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization, Inc. (New York, NY), 1972-1973; 300305 (Box 46)
  - Inter-union Institute for Labor and Democracy (New York, NY), 1945; 300030 (Box 46)
  - Inter-union Institute on Labor and Defense, 1944; 300306 (Box 46)
  - Inter-Varsity Christian Coalition, 374329 (Box 46)
  - Iranian Students Association of America I, 1976-; 300307 (Box 46)
  - Iranian Students Association of America II, 1976-; 324488 (Box 46)
  - Irish-American Labor Coalition, 1985; 324489 (Box 46)
  - Irish Communist Organization, 1971; 380080 (Box 46)
  - Iron Curtain Refugee Campaign (New York, NY), 1952; 300308 (Box 46)
  - Israeleft News Service (Jerusalem), 1973; 324490 (Box 46)
  - Israeli Committee Against House Demolitions, 2011; 423052 (Box 46)
  - Italian American Labor Council, Inc. I, 1942-; 300310 (Box 47)
  - Italian American Labor Council, Inc. II, 1942-; 300311 (Box 47)
  - Italian American Labor Council, Inc. III, 1942-; 300312 (Box 47)
  - Italian Emergency Rescue Committee (New York, NY), undated; 300313 (Box 47)
  - Italian Federation of Labor (Battaglie Sindicali) (serial), 1931; 324492 (Box 47)
  - Italian Federation of the Socialist Party (Chicago, IL), undated; 300314 (Box 47)
  - Italian Socialist Party (Partito Socialista Italiano) (in English and Italian), undated; 305477 (Box 47)
  - Izquierda Cristiana (Chile), 1974; 305843 (Box 47)
- J, 300309
  - Jabhah al-Sha_b_iyah li-Ta_hr_ir _Um_an, 1976; 300315 (Box 47)
  - Jackrabbit Woman's Press, 1975; 300316 (Box 47)
  - Jackson Youth Movement, undated; 300317 (Box 47)
  - Jamaican Movement for the Advancement of Literacy (JAMAL) I, 1977, undated; 324493 (Box 47)
  - Jamaican Movement for the Advancement of Literacy (JAMAL) II, 1977, undated; 327900 (Box 47)
  - James J. Bambrick Jr. and Associates (New York, NY) (industrial relations consultants), 1941; 300318 (Box 47)
  - Jane Addams Peace Association (New York, NY), 1961; 300319 (Box 47)
  - Jane Addams Peace School (New York, NY), undated; 300320 (Box 47)
  - Jane Doe Books (Brooklyn, NY), 2000-; 300321 (Box 47)
  - Japan Council Against A&H Bombs, circa 1960s; 300322 (Box 47)
  - Japan "Peace for Vietnam!" Committee, 1965; 305260 (Box 47)
  - Japanese American Committee for Democracy (New York, NY), circa 1945; 300323 (Box 47)
  - Japanese Red Army (Nihon Sekigun), 1979; 301908 (Box 47)
  - Japanese Youth Fatherland Front, 1951; 300324 (Box 47)
  - Jean Field Committee, undated; 327874 (Box 47)
  - Jeannette Rankin Brigade, undated; 373712 (Box 47)
  - Jeanette Rankin Rank and File (anti-Vietnam War), 1968; 300325 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson Book Shop (New York, NY), undated; 300326 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1945-1946; 300327 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1947-1948; 300328 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1949; 300329 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1951-1952; 300330 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1953; 300331 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), 1954-1955; 300332 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY) I, undated; 300333 (Box 47)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY) II, undated; 300334 (Box 47)
  - Jesus Radicals, 2003; 324494 (Box 47)
  - Jeune Socialiste Ouvrier et Paysan, undated; 300335 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Affairs, 1946-1986; 372989 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Americans for World Peace (New York, NY), 1984; 300336 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Anarchist Committee, 1986; 300337 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Anarchist Community (New York, NY), 1982; 300338 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Campaign to End the Indochina Holocaust, undated; 374755 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Consumptives' Relief Society, 1948; 324495 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents, 1959-1969; 300339 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents I, 1970-1979; 300340 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents II, 1970-1979; 300341 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents, 1980-1989; 300349 (Box 47)
  - Jewish Currents, 1990-1999; 300350 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Currents, 2000-; 300351 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Daily Forward, 1927-; 300352 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Defense League, undated; 327875 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Federation-Council of Greater Los Angeles, undated; 422908 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Bund, 1955-1961, undated; 324496 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1940-1949; 300353 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1940-1949; 300354 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee III, 1940-1949; 324497 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1950-1959; 300355 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1950-1959; 300356 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee III, 1950-1959; 300357 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee IV, 1950-1959; 300358 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1960-1969; 300359 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1970-1979; 300360 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1970-1979; 300361 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1980-1989; 300368 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1980-1989; 300369 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1990-1993; 300370 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1990-1993; 300371 (Box 48)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 1994-1999; 300372 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 1994-1999; 300373 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee III, 1994-1999; 300374 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee I, 2000-; 300375 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee II, 2000-; 300376 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee III, 2000-; 300377 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee IV, 2000-; 324522 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, undated; 300378 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Labor Committee: Pamphlets and Brochures, 1940-; 324523 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Liberation Project (New York, NY), 1969-1971; 300379 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Life (New York, NY), 1953, undated; 300380 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Minorities Research (New York, NY), 1961-1962; 300381 (Box 49)
  - Jewish National Fund, 1958; 324524 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peace Fellowship (New York, NY), undated; 300382 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Committee, circa 1930-1942; 300383 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order Cooperative Book League, 1944; 372990 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order of the IWO (U.S.), 1968-; 300385 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order of the IWO (U.S.): Jewish Children's Schools of Philadelphia Yearbooks I, 1951-1961; 306941 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order of the IWO (U.S.): Jewish Children's Schools of Philadelphia Yearbooks II, 1951-1961; 306942 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Publication and Research Committee (New York, NY), 1954; 300384 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Radical Education Project, 1990-; 300386 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Reconstructionist Foundation, undated; 327876 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Sisterhood's Day Nursery and Neighborhood House (Newark, NJ), 1915-1916; 324525 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Socialist Community (New York, NY), 1973-1974; 300387 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Socialist Federation of America, undated; 300388 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Socialist Group, undated; 372991 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Socialist Verband of America, 1932-1946; 300389 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Socialist Youth Bund (New York, NY), undated; 300390 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Socialist Youth Club "Zukunft", 1942; 327877 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Trade Union Organization Committee (Chicago, IL), undated; 300391 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Women's Committee to End Occupation of the West Bank and Gaza, 1989-; 324526 (Box 49)
  - Jewish Young Fraternalists, 1949-; 300392 (Box 49)
  - Jews Against the Occupation, 2000-; 300393 (Box 49)
  - Jews for Jesus, undated; 324527 (Box 49)
  - Jews for Justice in the Middle East, undated; 372992 (Box 50)
  - Jews for Racial and Economic Justice (New York, NY), 1993-; 300394 (Box 50)
  - Jews Say No, 387521 (Box 50)
  - Jews Uniting to End the War and Heal America, 2008; 324536 (Box 50)
  - Jim Hayes Defense Fund, 1969; 373676 (Box 50)
  - Job is a Right Campaign (U.S.), undated; 300395 (Box 50)
  - Jobless-Liberty Party, undated; 300396 (Box 50)
  - Jobs with Justice (U.S.) I, 1991-; 300397 (Box 50)
  - Jobs with Justice (U.S.) II, 1991-; 324537 (Box 50)
  - Jobs with Peace (Boston, MA), 1986-, undated; 300398 (Box 50)
  - Johannes Steel Report on World Affairs (New York, NY), undated; 301909 (Box 50)
  - John Birch Society, 1960s; 324538 (Box 50)
  - John Brown Anti-Klan Committee, 1982, undated; 324539 (Box 50)
  - John Brown Book Club (Seattle, WA), 1977-; 300399 (Box 50)
  - John Brown College (South Kortright, NY), 1966; 300400 (Box 50)
  - John Brown Party (Tucson, AZ), 1969; 300401 (Box 50)
  - John Brown Revolutionary League, 1970; 300402 (Box 50)
  - John Brown Society, 1990-; 300403 (Box 50)
  - John Crempa Defense Committee (Newark, NJ), undated; 300404 (Box 50)
  - John Day Company, 1932; 423085 (Box 50)
  - John Hay Whitney Foundation, 1952-1974; 300405 (Box 50)
  - John Reed Club, 1930-1938; 300406 (Box 50)
  - John Williamson Defence Campaign, 1955; 372993 (Box 50)
  - John Yezbak and Company, 1958, undated; 300407 (Box 50)
  - Johnson-Forest Tendency, 1942-1947; 300408 (Box 50)
  - JOIN Community Union (Chicago, IL), 1967-1969; 300409 (Box 50)
  - Join Hands (San Francisco, CA), 1977; 305841 (Box 50)
  - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, 1942-1952; 300410 (Box 50)
  - Joint Board of Sanitary Control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and the Dress and Waist Industries, 1911-1913; 304608 (Box 50)
  - Joint Boycott Council of the American Jewish Congress and Jewish Labor Committee, 1936-1938; 300411 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee for Passaic Defense, undated; 437210 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee for Repeal of the Ives Loyalty Oath Law, undated; 300412 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee for Student Action, undated; 327879 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee for the April 5th Peace Rally (Washington DC), 1940; 324540 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee for the Defense of the Brazilian People, 1938; 300413 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee of the Russian Co-operatives Organisations, 1920; 305249 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee on Direct Legislation (Oregon), undated; 300414 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee on Transit (New York City transit crisis), 1969; 324541 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee on Unemployment, undated; 300415 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee to Fight Discriminatory Hiring Practices in the New York Hotel Industry, undated; 324542 (Box 50)
  - Joint Committee to Secure a Fair Trial for the Trenton Six, circa 1951; 327880 (Box 50)
  - Joint Council for International Cooperation, 1946; 324543 (Box 50)
  - Joint Demonstration Committee, 1932; 324544 (Box 50)
  - Joint Distribution Campaign Committee, undated; 324545 (Box 50)
  - Joint Self-Defense Committee (Smith Act), 1956, undated; 300416 (Box 50)
  - Joint United States-Mexico Trade Union Committee, 1956; 300417 (Box 50)
  - Jose Marti Publishing House (Cuba), 1989; 372994 (Box 50)
  - Joseph Fels Fund of America (Cincinnati, OH), 1912-1913; 300418 (Box 50)
  - Joseph S. Murphy Institute for Worker Education and Labor Studies (New York, NY), 2007-; 300419 (Box 50)
  - Joseph Weydemeyer School of Social Science, undated; 300420 (Box 50)
  - Joventut Socialista Unificada de Catalunya, 1946; 300421 (Box 50)
  - Juan Farinas Defense Committee (New York, NY), undated; 300422 (Box 50)
  - Judge Armstrong Foundation (Fort Worth, TX), 1948; 300423 (Box 50)
  - Judson Memorial Church (New York, NY), 2002-; 300424 (Box 50)
  - July 4th Coalition, 1976; 300425 (Box 50)
  - July 7th Organizing Committee, 1990; 327881 (Box 50)
  - July 26th Coalition/Movement (Cuban revolution, anniversary), 2003-, undated; 300426 (Box 50)
  - June 12th Rally Committee, 1982; 375403 (Box 50)
  - Junta of Militant Organizations (St. Petersburg, FL), 1970-1971; 300427 (Box 50)
  - Just Food (New York, NY), 1999-; 300428 (Box 50)
  - Justice for Detainees (Brooklyn, NY), 2002-; 300430 (Box 50)
  - Justice for Greece Committee (Washington, DC), 1946; 300431 (Box 50)
  - Justice for Janitors Organizing Committee, undated; 324546 (Box 50)
  - Justice for Jazz Artists, 1997; 324547 (Box 50)
  - Justice for Youth Coalition/ nomoreyouthjails.org, undated; 324548 (Box 50)
  - Justice Will Be Served: Boycott, 2008-; 324549 (Box 50)
  - Justseeds, undated; 324550 (Box 50)
  - Justus Legal Collective, 2000-; 300429 (Box 50)
- K, 304706
  - Kampuchea Support Committee (New York, NY), undated; 300432 (Box 50)
  - Kansas Freedom from Hunger Committee, undated; 374763 (Box 50)
  - Karl Armstrong Defense Fund, undated; 374217 (Box 50)
  - Kartemquin Educational Films (Chicago, IL), 1982; 300435 (Box 50)
  - Kasama Project, 387522 (Box 50)
  - Kate Sharpley Library (London), 1984-; 300433 (Box 50)
  - Kaweah Co-operative Colony, 1891; 300434 (Box 50)
  - Keep America Out of War Congress I, 1938-1941; 300436 (Box 50)
  - Keep America Out of War Congress II, 1938-1941; 300437 (Box 50)
  - Kensington Welfare Rights Union, 2002, undated; 372995 (Box 50)
  - Kent Legal Defense Fund (Ohio), 1970; 300438 (Box 50)
  - Kent State Anti-War Committee (Ohio), 2002; 300439 (Box 50)
  - Kentucky Miners' Defense: Harlan County, KY, 1936-1937, undated; 314148 (Box 51)
  - Keren Hayesod (Palestine Foundation Fund) (New York, NY), 1944-1945; 300440 (Box 51)
  - Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives (Cornell University, Ithaca, NY), undated; 300441 (Box 51)
  - Khmer Residents in America, 1970; 374340 (Box 51)
  - King-Ramsey-Conner Defense Committee (San Francisco, CA), 1940; 300442 (Box 51)
  - Kips Bay Neighborhood Association, undated; 324566 (Box 51)
  - Klanwatch Project (Montgomery, AL), 1980-1983; 300443 (Box 51)
  - Knights of Labor, 1885-1888, circa 1940s-1983; 323272 (Box 51)
  - Know, Inc., 1971-1976, undated; 324583 (Box 51)
  - Konferenz Der Kommunistischen Und Arbeiterparteien (Berlin, Germany), 1976; 300444 (Box 51)
  - Korea Today, 1970; 380081 (Box 51)
  - Korean Democratic Women's Union, 1968; 380082 (Box 51)
  - Korean Democratic Women's Union in Japan (Tokyo) (Yomeng), 1987; 372996 (Box 51)
  - Kropotkin Society (Evansville, IN), 1975; 300445 (Box 51)
  - Kropotkin's Lighthouse Publications (London), 1970-1971, undated; 300446 (Box 51)
- L, 300458
  - La Lutta New Media Collective, circa 1998; 300447 (Box 51)
  - Labadie (Joseph) Collection (Harlan Hatcher Graduate Library), 2002; 300448 (Box 51)
  - Labor Action for Peace, 1962; 300450 (Box 51)
  - Labor Action School (New York, NY), 1949; 300451 (Box 51)
  - Labor Age (New York, NY), 1929; 300452 (Box 51)
  - Labor and Working Class History Association (LAWCHA), 2002-; 300449 (Box 51)
  - Labor Anti-War Council, undated; 300453 (Box 51)
  - Labor Art and Mural Project, undated; 373002 (Box 51)
  - Labor Arts, 2001-; 300454 (Box 51)
  - Labor at the Crossroads, 2002-; 300455 (Box 51)
  - Labor Black League for Social Defense, 2003, undated; 324567 (Box 51)
  - Labor Bureau, Inc., 1925-1930; 300456 (Box 51)
  - Labor Chest for Relief and Liberation of Workers of Europe, 1935-1937, undated; 300457 (Box 51)
  - Labor Club, 1939; 324568 (Box 51)
  - Labor College of Philadelphia, 1928; 300459 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee for Goldberg-Paterson, 1970; 300460 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee for Human Rights, undated; 327882 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee for Peace in Vietnam, 1966; 300461 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee for Peaceful Alternatives, 1955; 300462 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee for Safe Energy and Full Employment, 1981; 300463 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee for Thomas and Maurer, undated; 300464 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee of the Detroit Coalition to End the War Now, undated; 373003 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee on El Salvador and Central America, 1989; 300465 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance, 1948; 324569 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee to Elect William O'Dwyer, 1938; 324570 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee to Release Imprisoned Trade Unionists and Democratic Socialists, 1958-1960, undated; 300466 (Box 51)
  - Labor Committee for the Suspended Furriers, 1940; 300467 (Box 51)
  - Labor Defense Congress for the Samuel Kelly Defense Committee, undated; 300468 (Box 51)
  - Labor Education and Research Project (U.S.), 1986-1998; 300469 (Box 51)
  - Labor Education Association (Philadelphia, PA), undated; 300470 (Box 51)
  - Labor Education Committee, undated; 300471 (Box 51)
  - Labor Education Fund, Inc., undated; 327883 (Box 51)
  - Labor Education Service, 1943, undated; 324571 (Box 51)
  - Labor Educational Center, 1942; 300472 (Box 51)
  - Labor Educator (Harry Kelber) I, 1997-; 300473 (Box 51)
  - Labor Educator (Harry Kelber) II, 1997-; 324572 (Box 51)
  - Labor Environment Alliance for Planetary Solidarity (LEAPS) (anti big oil), undated; 300474 (Box 51)
  - Labor Features Syndicate, 1952; 324573 (Box 51)
  - Labor for Equal Rights Now, 1979; 327884 (Box 51)
  - Labor for Goldwater (Barry), 1960s; 300475 (Box 51)
  - Labor for Peace Conference (St. Louis, MO), 1972; 300476 (Box 51)
  - Labor Forum (New York, NY), 1917; 453031 (Box 51)
  - Labor Heritage Foundation, 1985-; 300477 (Box 51)
  - Labor Institute (New York, NY), 1985-; 300478 (Box 51)
  - Labor League for Human Rights, 1941-1946; 300479 (Box 51)
  - Labor League for Thomas and Nelson, undated; 300480 (Box 51)
  - Labor Media Forum (formerly NYC Labor Film Club), 1986; 300481 (Box 51)
  - Labor Militant (New York City fiscal crisis), 1995; 324574 (Box 51)
  - Labor Movement Library and Archive (Denmark), 1993-; 300482 (Box 51)
  - Labor Notes, 1982, 1995; 324575 (Box 51)
  - Labor Notes: Conferences, 1990-1995; 324576 (Box 51)
  - Labor Occupational Health Program (Berkeley, CA), 1997; 300483 (Box 51)
  - Labor Organizers Defense Fund, 1974-1977; 300484 (Box 51)
  - Labor Party, 1939-; 324577 (Box 51)
  - Labor Party Advocates (U.S.), 1993-; 300485 (Box 51)
  - Labor Party Advocates (U.S.): New York Metro Chapter, 1996, undated; 324578 (Box 51)
  - Labor Party Association (U.S.), undated; 300486 (Box 51)
  - Labor Party League, 1975; 300487 (Box 51)
  - Labor Party of Chicago and Cook County (Illinois), 1919-1930s, undated; 300488 (Box 51)
  - Labor Party of the United States of America: First National Convention, 1919; 324579 (Box 51)
  - Labor Press Associates (Washington, DC), 1948; 300489 (Box 52)
  - Labor Progressive Party, 1946-1957, undated; 324580 (Box 52)
  - Labor Project for Working Families, 1997; 300490 (Box 52)
  - Labor Publications, Inc. (Oak Park, MI) I, 1971-1975; 300491 (Box 52)
  - Labor Publications, Inc. (Oak Park, MI) II, 1971-1975; 300492 (Box 52)
  - Labor Publications, Inc. (Oak Park, MI) III, 1971-1975; 324581 (Box 52)
  - Labor Reports (reprints), undated; 300493 (Box 52)
  - Labor Research Association, circa 1940; 300494 (Box 52)
  - Labor Research Association, 1970s-1982; 300495 (Box 52)
  - Labor Research Association, 1983-1985; 300496 (Box 52)
  - Labor Research Association: Pamphlets, 1929-1978; 300497 (Box 52)